{
     "questions": [
          {
               "answers": [
                    "MyClass.jv",
                    "MyClass.java",
                    "MyClass.js"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "MyClass.java",
               "id": 0,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "A file containing a class called MyClass should be saved as:",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 1,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Java is case-sensitive: 'MyClass' and 'myclass' has different meaning.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "An Object",
                    "A header file library",
                    "A namespace",
                    "A function"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "A header file library",
               "id": 2,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "What is #include <iostream>?",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 3,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "C++ is case-sensitive: 'main' and 'Main' has different meaning.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "Error because it is missing using namespace std;",
                    "Error because it uses std::",
                    "Hello World!",
                    "std"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "Hello World!",
               "id": 4,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "What is the output of the following code? \\n #include <iostream> int main() {std::cout << \\\"Hello World!\\\"; return 0;}",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 5,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "In C++, each code statement must end with a semicolon (;).",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "Hello World!",
                    "cout",
                    "Error"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "Error",
               "id": 6,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "What is the output of the following code? cout << \"Hello World!\"",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "Hello World!",
                    "cout",
                    "Error"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "Hello World!",
               "id": 7,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "What is the output of the following code? cout << \"Hello World!\";",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 8,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "Statements are executed, one by one, in the same order as they are written.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 9,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "In Java, each code statement must end with a semicolon (;).",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "println()",
                    "printline()",
                    "printtext()",
                    "echo()"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "println()",
               "id": 10,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Which method is often used to print text in Java?",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "True",
               "id": 11,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Text inside println() must be wrapped inside double quotes.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "The println() method adds a line break after printing, while print() does not",
                    "The print() method adds a line break after printing, while println() does not"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "The println() method adds a line break after printing, while print() does not",
               "id": 12,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "The difference between println() and print() is that:",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "3",
                    "6",
                    "9"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "6",
               "id": 13,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "What is the output of the following code? System.out.println(3 + 3);",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "False",
               "id": 14,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Numbers inside println() must be wrapped inside double quotes.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "2",
                    "25",
                    "10",
                    "5"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "10",
               "id": 15,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "What is the output of the following code? System.out.println(2 * 5);",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "To output text",
                    "To create text variables",
                    "To explain and document code",
                    "To print text and numbers with a simple line of code"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "To explain and document code",
               "id": 16,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "What is the meaning of comments in Java?",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    ".pp",
                    ".pt",
                    ".py"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": ".py",
               "id": 17,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "What is the correct file extension for Python files?",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "python --version",
                    "python ##version",
                    "python version"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "python --version",
               "id": 18,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "What is a correct command line syntax for checking if python is installed on your computer? (And also to check the Python version)",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "exit()",
                    "stop()",
                    "end()"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "exit()",
               "id": 19,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "What is a correct syntax to exit the Python command line interface?",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "False",
               "id": 20,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "Indentation in Python is for readability only.",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "(\"Hello World\")"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "print",
               "id": 21,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "Insert the missing part of the code below to output \"Hello World\"",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "carName = \"Volvo\";"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "String",
               "id": 22,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Create a variable named carName and assign the value Volvo to it.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "maxSpeed = 120;"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "int",
               "id": 23,
               "language": 0,
               "question": "Create a variable named maxSpeed and assign the value 120 to it.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "<< 10 * 5;"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "cout",
               "id": 24,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "Multiply 10 with 5, and print the result.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "x"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "++",
               "id": 25,
               "language": 1,
               "question": "Use the correct operator to increase the value of the variable int x = 10; by 1.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "= \"Volvo\""
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "carname",
               "id": 26,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "Create a variable named carname and assign the value Volvo to it.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "= 50"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "x",
               "id": 27,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "Create a variable named x and assign the value 50 to it.",
               "type": 1
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "35",
                    "35.88",
                    "36"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "35",
               "id": 28,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "What will be the result of the following code: print(int(35.88))",
               "type": 0
          },
          {
               "answers": [
                    "print(dtype(x))",
                    "print(type(x))",
                    "print(x.dtype())"
               ],
               "correctAnswer": "print(type(x))",
               "id": 29,
               "language": 2,
               "question": "If x = 5, what is a correct syntax for printing the data type of the variable x?",
               "type": 0
          }
     ]
}